KATELYN DUNN

714-463-5653 katelyndunn2020@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/katelyn-dunn-20 github.com/jiuijtsufarmer

About Me

I enjoy structure, problem solving, and organizing data. I've worked with various tools and technologies, such as SQL IDE and Quickbooks. I've also done some light web development and robotics.

Data Analyst Experience

Data Analyst Apprentice – Nashville Software School Sep 2020 - Jan 2021

Work Experience

Package Handler – UPS Jun 2020 – Sep 2020

- in charge of bagging smaller boxes
- made sure boxes were heading to the right location

Rocket Nine Intern — Rocket Nine Solutions Mar 2015 – Jun 2020

- In charge of payroll and taking care of late payments.
- did light web development
- taught robotics in the CSM classes

Package Handler – FedEx

Oct 2019 - Mar 2020

- loaded semi trailers
- · made sure the boxes made it to the right trailer

Data Verification Clerk - SurePrep

Feb 2019 - Apr 2019

• analyzed, compared, and corrected tax documents before sending them back to clients

Education

LearningFuze — HTML Root Class

The HTML Root Class introduces students to key fundamental concepts such as HTML syntax, CSS syntax, CSS selectors, JavaScript variables, JavaScript functions, JavaScript objects, JavaScript conditionals, JavaScript loops, and more.

Nashville Software School - Analytics Jumpstart

Covers the fundamentals of Python, SQL, Jupiter Notebooks, Exploratory Data Analysis, and Data Visualization.

Nashville Software School - Data Analytics Bootcamp

Focuses on Python, Spreadsheets, SQL, Workflow, Exploratory Data Analysis, and Dashboards to create a well-rounded Data Analyst. The curriculum also includes real-world projects for the students to work on.

Projects

App Trader

- set out to find the best, low risk apps to invest in
- pgAdmin

UN Data

- looked at gdp and internet usage data for a correlation
- Jupyter Notebook

Skills

SQL • Tableau • pgAdmin • Jupyter Notebook • Python • Excel • Power BI